chat-work.com 2012-12-02

# Privacy policy｜ChatWork

Last Updated: December 26, 2011

ChatWork Inc is committed to protecting your privacy. We hope that you will take the time to read this Privacy Policy, which explains what information we collect from you and how we use that information. By visiting our website or using the ChatWork ™ service (the “service”) you agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy. Please check back frequently, as this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. 

When you visit our website or use the service, ChatWork Inc collects your IP address, which we use to improve our services as well as to help us administer our website and the service and diagnose technical problems. Your IP address may also be used to gather broad demographic information that does not personally identify you. In order to use the service, you must set up an ChatWork Inc account by providing us with your name, email address, company name and a chosen password. We may also collect any information that you may provide to us in response to customer surveys. We may use your e-mail address or your ChatWork account to occasionally notify you about your unread messages, important changes to our website and the service, new features, available upgrades, special offers that you may find useful, or offers from companies with whom we have business relationships. 

Other users of the service may view your name and ChatWork ID (as well as your photograph, if you have posted one) unless you un-select “Allow your profile to show up in searches” in the “Your profile” menu in “Settings”. 

The service allows you to enter your user IDs for Facebook, Skype and Twitter if you wish. Your Facebook, Skype and Twitter IDs will be visible to other users of the service that you have entered in your “Contacts” list. 

To protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control we have implemented security measures on the website and the service. 

Payments for Personal Plans and Business Plans are made through the PayPal service. ChatWork Inc has no access to information you submit to PayPal, and has no responsibility for the security of such information. 

Except as described in this Privacy Policy, ChatWork Inc will not share your personal information with third parties unless you have consented to the disclosure or the disclosure is necessary to: 

  1. (1) Comply with the law or with legal process, or with requests from law enforcement authorities;
  2. (2) Protect and defend our rights and property;
  3. (3) Protect our customers or users from misuse or unauthorized use of the our website or the service; or 
  4. (4) Protect the personal safety or property of our customers or the public. 

ChatWork Inc may share your personal information with other companies in our corporate group. Also, if ChatWork Inc is acquired by or merges with another company, ChatWork Inc may transfer personal information to that company. In such an event, ChatWork Inc will notify you before your personal data is transferred if this information would become subject to a materially different privacy policy. 

ChatWork Inc may provide aggregate statistics about our customers, sales, traffic patterns, and related information to third parties, but these statistics will not include any personally identifying information. 

Our website and the service may contain links, log-in interfaces, and other connections to third-party websites and applications (including websites, widgets, software, and other software utilities) (“application(s)”). If you use an application to share information about you, your actions on our website or through the service, you are consenting to such information being shared. Your use of an application may cause personally identifying information to be publicly disclosed and/or associated with you, even if ChatWork Inc has not provided such information. Each application's privacy policy (and not this Privacy Policy) will govern information collected by such application. In addition, ChatWork Inc may allow you to log in to portions of our website and the service using applications provided by Facebook, Inc. (“ **Facebook** ”), Google Inc., LinkedIn Corporation, mixi, Inc., tumblr, Inc., Twitter, Inc., Windows Live by Microsoft, Yahoo! Inc. and other third-party services and other third-party services, and may allow you to use other third-party applications and features, such as a Facebook “Like” button. Through these applications and features, you may use information from these third-party accounts on our website and share activities and other information related to our website and the service through those third-party websites. By your use of those third-party applications, our website and the service may have access to information related to the third-party accounts (including your profile information, “friends,” and privacy settings) and the third-party services may receive information concerning actions you take on our website. The privacy policy and terms of use of those third-party services apply to their use of information collected by or provided to them through such applications and features and this Privacy Policy applies to ChatWork Inc's use of information collected by or provided to ChatWork Inc through third-party applications and features. 

You may change your profile picture (should you choose to upload one), display name, company/organization name, email address, password, and ChatWork ID (subject to availability) at any time. To do this, simply click on your user name in the upper right corner of the screen, select “Settings” and “Your profile”. 

The ChatWork Inc website may contain links to other sites, operated by third parties that we believe may be of interest to you. While ChatWork Inc encourages third parties to follow appropriate privacy standards and policies, it is not responsible for the actions of those parties, the content of their websites or any products or services they may offer. 

The ChatWork Inc website employs “cookies,” which are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Our cookies enable us to store your plan information between visits and facilitate your use of the website and the service. 

If you have set your browser to reject cookies, you can still use our site, although you may need to re-enter information that would normally be obtained from the cookie. 

At ChatWork Inc, we believe that the privacy of children is important. 

We do not monitor the age of our users except in connection with surveys and contests. However, visitors and users under the age of thirteen (13) should not submit personal identifying information to ChatWork Inc or through the service without the consent of their parent(s) or guardian(s). If a user is under the age of thirteen (13) the user may not, even under the supervision of a parent or guardian, register for the service or otherwise submit any information to the ChatWork Inc website or the service. 

Please check back frequently, as this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. The date of the most recent update to the Privacy Policy will be indicated at the top of this page. In the event of a material change to the Privacy Policy, for a reasonable time after such change we will add “Updated”, “New”, or a similar term near the link to the Privacy Policy on the home page of ChatWork Inc and elsewhere, as applicable, throughout our website. 

If you have any questions or suggestions, please contact us at privacy@chatwork.com, or by mail at the address below: 

Privacy Director  
ChatWork Inc  
440 North Wolfe Road Sunnyvale, CA 94085
